

0723 014 344

mww.sebastianc.design



SUMMARY

As a front-end developer with skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React and more, I aim to provide an easier experience for the users and to focus on their problems firstly, rather than on the technical ones. Willing to continuously gather new skills and expand my actual ones, I do everything to stay up-to-date with the latest technologies of the mad, but beautiful, front-end development world.

n /in/sebastianciobanu

♥ @s3bastian43

/s3bastian43



WORK EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

SIVECO | Sept 2018 - Present

Bucharest, Romania

My role within the company is to analyse, test and develop back-end and front-end code for the multiple projects I am working on.

JUNIOR WEB DESIGNER

Easitill | Oct 2017 - June 2018

Brixworth, United Kingdom

My responsibilities included the designing, the prototyping and the development of e-commerce and brochure websites, as well as improving brand identity, SEO and performance.

PROJECTS

THE FUTURE | 2018

Clothing Store built using WooCommerce the-fut-ure.com

UNIPLANNER | 2018

Student planner and team collaboration web application created so that the users can keep track of their course, as well as collaborate by sharing notes and creating tasks.

uniplanner.co.uk

HOME-START NORTHAMPTON | 2017-2018

Working in a team of four, the WordPress CMS was used to develop a website that reflects and promotes the support offered by the charity.

• homestart-northampton.org.uk



EDUCATION

BSc BUSINESS COMPUTING (WEB DESIGN)

University of Northampton | 2015 - 2018

Northampton, United Kingdom

AWARDS

- Most promising first year student on BSc Business Computing at The University of Northampton | 2016
- High Achievers A Level Scholarship | 2015



SKILLS

Web Development

HTML5 WordPress
CSS3 | SASS Drupal
JavaScript | jQuery Jekyll
React.js Bootstrap
Node.js | Express.js MDL
PHP Pug.js
GitHub | CLI SQL | MySQ

Design

Photoshop
Illustrator
InDesign
Iconography

• UX | UI Design

Material Design
Flat Design
Microinteractions
Storymapping
Emotional Interactio

IDE | Prototyping

Visual Studio Code
JetBrains IDEs
Sublime
Balsamiq
XD

Axure RP
Justinmind

InVision App



REFERENCES

Liz Coulter-Smith | Senior Lecturer in Computing University of Northampton

+44 (0) 7948 559923 | ecoultersmith@gmail.com

Claire Harris | Web Designer Easitill

01604 881881 | claire@easitill.co.uk